Today we will look at ten unusual and maybe too
A little stupid way people have died.
We can start in Sweden in 1771.
The then king of Sweden, Adolf Fredrik,
Had for some time had problems with their health.
Headaches, migraine attacks, stomach pain and colds that came and went.
And a beautiful day, February 12, 1771
ate the king to death.
Yes, you heard right.
The meal that became his death consisted of sauerkraut,
Meat, root vegetables, lobster, caviar, Böckling.
The kind of fish and rinsed everything with champagne.
and fell lifeless to the floor.
The big meal had given him a stroke and he
is now forever known as "the king who ate to death"
Garry Hoy
Was a lawyer in Toronto who in 1993 was involved in an accident.
He worked on the 24th floor of a skyscraper called Toronto
Dominion Center and Gary was fascinated
over how large the windows the building had.
While working there he had come to a small party trick there
He threw himself at the windows to show how safe and robust they were.
One day July 9, 1993,
Had the law firm study visit and Garry gave law
Students a tour and decided to make their party trick
to impress the students.
They took the batch, threw themselves against one of the windows,
But instead of bouncing against the window as usual
So the window loosened from the frame where it was stuck
And Garry went out and fell 24 floors down to his death.
January 6, 2015 in Taiwan.
A 32 year old man whose last name was "Hsieh", stepped into an Internet café.
He was a regular customer there and often played for several days in a row.
Employees have said that when he got tired he slept in his chair.
But this time his visit to the Internet Café would be the last.
Hsieh sat down at a computer and started playing.
He played nonstop for a whole three days.
After these three days the body was able
had invented something he thought would revolutionize the aviation industry.
He had invented a type of parachute suit.
It was supposed to act as a normal flight suit, but that it quickly
could be triggered to be used as a parachute in an emergency.
It could save life
on pilots whose aircraft suffered any technical error.
February 4th of the 20th century he would demonstrate his invention
Public and the demonstration would be carried out from the Eiffel Tower.
From the beginning he had intended to conduct the test with a doll,
But decided at the last moment to conduct the test itself.
It would seem more convincing, he thought.
So February 4th he climbed up to the Eiffel Tower
First ledge that is about 60 meters above the ground and threw themselves out.
But the suit did not work and Franz
fell straight down into the ground and died immediately.
In front of audiences and journalists who had gathered on the site.
Tycho
Brahe was a Danish astronomer who lived late
during the 16th century and just in the early 17th century.
October 13, 1601 participated
He at a big dinner event in Prague.
According to this story, Tycho drank a lot during this party,
but refused to leave the dinner table to go to the toilet
Because he felt it was rude to leave the table before the party was over.
This made him held from urinating for several hours
And it led to a massive overpowered fermentation in the bladder.
When the party was over he could not urinate properly even though he
really needed, and eleven days after dinner he died
only 54 years old.
The cause of death may have been urine poisoning
and/or urinary tract infection.
born 1877 in San Francisco, USA, was a
Well -known dancer who was considered to be the founder of modern dance.
But it was not only her dance that made her known, but also her death.
September 14, 1927, in Nice
In France, she was on her way home after an evening out in town.
She sat as a passenger in her Amilcar
CG SS that she had given the nickname Bugatti.
A car that had no roof.
That night, IsaDora wore a long scarf of silk and as she sat
There in the car and went, the long scarf blew with the wind behind her.
Somehow the scarf managed to get stuck in one of the rear tires.
She quickly wrapped herself around the deck.
The scarf stretched back and stretched her
And with a violent force, she was withdrawn from the open car.
to and fell forward straight down
On the drink she held in her hand.
The straw went in through her one eye and then
into the brain which caused her death.
19182i Arizona, USA, was basically man
And his friend out in the desert to shoot cacti.
A little for fun like that.
They used to do this activity together and their goals were the
so -called saguaroaktus that can be up
to twelve meters high and weigh several tons.
When David shot one of these cacti, it was broken by ... fell ..